Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
可愛いね
That's not true.
そんなことないですよ
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
i want to eat.
食べたい
It's embarrassing when people say things like that.
恥ずかしいんですけど、 そんなこと言われると
Because I'm taking a lot of pictures.
いっぱい撮っちゃってるから
Have you ever photographed this?
これ撮られたことある?
It's my first time.
初めてです
Well, that's right.
まあ そうで
The uniform is super cute.
制服超可愛いね
This is cute, isn't it?
これ可愛いですよね
I chose this school because the uniform is cute.
この学校選んだの、 この制服が可愛いからで
Did you choose it based on the uniform?
制服で選んだの?
I chose it because of the uniform.
制服で選んだんですよ
Can I ask you some questions?
色々聞いてもいいですか?
yes.
はい
How old are you?
何歳?
I'm 10 years old.
10歳です
like?
若?
How old are you?
何年生?
I'm a 10th year high school student.
高校10年生です
It's really red.
めっちゃ赤いじゃん
I'm a hot JK.
ピチピチのJKです
Pichi pichi.
ピチピチ
Did it come in this year?
今年入ったもん?
I just arrived this year.
今年入ったばっかりです
A fun school?
楽しい学校?
School is really fun.
学校はめちゃ楽しいです
Many new places were created,
新しいところとかもたくさんできて、
It's quite fulfilling.
結構充実はしてます
That was good.
良かったね
What about studying?
勉強は?
Studying is
勉強は
I feel like I want to catch up.
追 いつけたいなって感じです
It's difficult, isn't it?
難しいよね
It's difficult.
難しくて
I see.
そうか
Do you have any club activities?
部活とかやってるの?
I joined the aquatic plant club.
部活は水草学入りました
That's good.
良いね
I want to see it.
見たい
I haven't done anything that big.
そんな大したことやってないです
Where do you work part-time?
バイトどこはしてるの?
My part-time job is as a store clerk in Mito.
バイトは水戸の店員さんやってます
This is Mito.
水戸です
Do you like donuts?
ドーナツ好きなの?
I like donuts.
ドーナツ好きで
I guess I've gained some weight.
若干太ってきちゃったかな
Like a little thick.
若 干 太みたいな
Because I'm not young.
若ないとかで
Can I have something to eat?
何か食べられるの?
Or rather, I'm not young.
若 ないというか、
You'll want to eat it.
食べ たくなっちゃうよね
It smells.
臭いとか
That's right.
そうなんですよ
Is that so?
そう か
It's fulfilling.
充実してるんだ
What do you do on your day off?
休みは何してるの?
I mostly play games during my free time.
休みはほぼゲームしてます
I like games.
ゲーム好きなんだ
ゲーム好きです
Like indoor?
インドアみたいな?
It's quite indoor.
結構インドアですね
Why don't you go on a date with your boyfriend?
彼氏とデート行かないの?
My boyfriend isn't very indoors, so
彼氏は、 あんまりインドアだから、
I don't go there that much.
そんなに行かないです
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いるんだ?
yes.
はい
Same school?
同じ学校?
It's the same school.
同じ学校です
Is it the same?
同いの?
yes.
はい
What if I even get a boyfriend?
彼氏まで作っちゃっても?
Your boyfriend will also be fulfilled.
彼氏も充実します
Hey.
ねえ
Did you do that kind of let's with your boyfriend?
彼氏とはそういう レッツアンドしたの?
Just recently?
つい最近?
first time?
初 めて?
It was my first time.
初めてしたんだ
how was it?
どうだった?
I was really nervous, but
すごい緊張したんですけど、
It's a bit embarrassing.
ちょっと なんか恥ずかしい
Please don't ask me that.
そんな聞かないで ください、そんな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Eh, I see.
えー、そっか
nice.
いいね
It's scary, a little.
怖いね、ちょっと
It makes me want to attack you, a little bit.
襲いたくなっちゃうね、ちょっと
What about trains?
電車とかなんつうなく?
It's a train.
電車ですね
Is it a mine train or something?
マイン電車とかなんですか?
Mine train, every day.
マイン電車です、毎日
You'll want to touch it.
触りたくなっちゃうよね
Ah, but something, something,
あー、でもなんか、 なんか、
Seriously?
マ ジで?
You probably spend your time with the same person every day.
毎日、たぶん同じ人に 時間されてるんですよ
Are you being touched?
触られてるの?
Touched or a little
触られたり、 ちょっと
That's right.
そう なんですよね
Are you scared?
怖いの?
very scary
すごい怖く
I'm looking for some kind of workaround.
て、 対処法みたいなの 探してるんですけど
Don't you appeal to that?
それの訴えしないの?
Please stop it, something like that.
やめてください、みたいな
I feel like it takes a lot of courage to say it out loud.
なんか、あんまり声に出すのが 勇気いるなって感じで、
I can't really say it.
なかなか言えなくて
Can you touch my underwear?
下着とか触られるの?
That's right.
そうなんですよ
It feels like it's direct.
なんか直接みたいな感じ
If it was a uniform.
なんか制服だったら
I wonder if that's so.
そうなのかなぁ
Let's think about that for a moment.
ちょっとそれは、 ちょっと考えよう
That's a problem.
困るもんね
Hey.
ねえ
I'm going to take some pictures today.
今日はちょっと、 いろいろ 撮っちゃうね
yes.
はい
That's scary.
怖いじゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしいです
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Don't be nervous.
緊張しないでよ
Do you have any dreams for the future?
将来の夢とかあるの?
In the future, I want to be a full-time housewife.
将来は、 専業主婦みたいな
Like a housewife?
専業主婦みたい?
yes.
はい
My hands are high.
手は高い
That's expensive.
高いね
It was said for the first time.
初めて言われました
copper?
どう?
Are you holding hands with your boyfriend?
彼氏と手を繋ぐの?
That will happen though.
それはなりますけど
How long have you been together?
付き合ってどんくらいなの?
We've been dating for about 2 months.
付き合って、 2ヶ月とか
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's been 2 months and it's already over?
2ヶ月なのにもうしちゃってんの?
I did it.
しちゃいました
What about Chu?
チューは?
I also had a chew.
チューもしました
Down?
下?
Like, put it in.
入 れてとか
Seriously?
マジ?
Is it now?
今ですか?
Rich...
濃厚な...
It's a rich chew.
濃厚なチューするんだね
boyfriend's house.
彼氏の家
Boyfriend's house?
彼氏の家?
When parents are not there.
親がいない時
It's smooth.
すべすべだね
Take care of me.
ケアしてよ
Please take care of me?
ケアしてよ?
Properly?
ちゃんと?
cute.
かわいい
amazing.
すごい
Will you?
するの?
Like before going to bed.
寝る前とか
Before going to bed?
寝る前?
How do you do it?
どんな風にするの?
Try it.
やってみて
Touch the parts from above?
パーツの上から触る?
put in.
入れる
put in?
入れる?
The top is also black.
上も黒だ
Touch it properly.
ちゃんと触るね
I want to touch it.
触りたいね
Would you rather touch yourself or be touched?
自分で触るのと触られるのがどっち?
I like being touched.
触られるのが好き
Would you rather be touched?
触られるほうがいいの?
It's getting really sticky.
すごいトロトロになってるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Do you look good?
顔いいの?
That's naughty.
やらしい
It's a beautiful area.
綺麗な地区だね
There is such a thing as beautiful.
綺麗とかあるんですね
There is.
あるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
A very naughty face.
すごいやらしい顔
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
amazing.
すごい
Put your feet out like this.
こうやって足につき出して
Have good feet.
いい足にして
That's naughty.
やらしいですね
Are you being touched there?
あそこで触られてるの?
How are you being touched?
どんなふうに触られてるの?
Are you touching me like this?
こんなに触るの?
Is that how you make your voice sound?
そうやって声出しちゃうの?
Do you let it out when someone is touching you on the train?
電車で触られてるときに出すの?
Does that feel good?
それ気持ちいいの?
Is that why you make that sound?
それでそんな声出しちゃうの?
Uncle can't stop doing that.
それはおじさんずっとやめられないよ
It seems so.
そうやらしい
It's small, amazing.
狭いね、すごい
Open your legs.
足開けて
It follows nicely.
綺麗に沿ってるね
By yourself.
自分で
For me, my boyfriend.
私、彼氏のために
With both hands.
両手でさ
It looks really good.
すごいよく見えるよ
Yeah?
うん?
delicious.
美味しい
amazing.
すごい
It's very narrow.
すごい狭い
Narrow
狭
Yes.
い ね
copper?
どう?
Oh, wow.
あ、やば
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Why so long ago?
なんでそんな前の?
I practiced.
練習した
practice?
練習?
Why did you practice?
なんで練習したの?
Did you work properly for someone who is not your boyfriend?
彼氏のために彼氏じゃない人の ちゃんと仕事してたの?
it is
それは
Hey, it's not an anise boat.
ちょっと、 アニスボートでないんだ
Isn't it a banana or something?
バナナとかでないの?
The one nearby?
近いやつ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Oh no, this is it.
やば、これ
acting
演じ
hand.
て
delicious?
美味 しい?
delicious.
美味しい
Oh, wow.
あ、やば
Very good at it.
すごい上手
A little bit on this side.
こっち側にちょこちょこ
Oh, I'm touching it.
あ、触ってる
terrible.
やばい
This is terrible.
やばいよ
delicious?
美味しい?
It's very choppy.
すごいちょこちょこってる
Arashi.
嵐ね
amazing.
すごい
Oh no.
やば
It's a little different.
ちょっと違う
Chinchi
ちんち
yeah.
ん
When was the last time you had it?
最近 いつイチしたの?
Not even a week.
一週間もない
It's been happening a lot lately.
めっちゃ最近してるね
Okay, with my boyfriend.
よいしょ、彼氏とね
With my boyfriend.
彼氏と
first time?
初めて?
first time.
初めて
Are you different from your boyfriend?
彼氏とは違うの?
I'm wearing it properly.
ちゃんとつけてる
Put it on properly.
ちゃんとつけるんだ
Tell me what you think.
感想教えて
Is it warm?
あったかい?
Isn't it warm?
あったかいでしょ?
It feels good, right?
気 持ちいいでしょ?
copper?
どう?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
I'll put it away over there.
あそこしまう
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいよね?
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
It's open.
開いてるね
Sorry, Zero Manko.
ごめんね、ゼロマン子
Here, let's go in.
ほら、入っちゃう
Look.
見て
Which feels better with your boyfriend?
彼氏とどっちが気持ちいい?
Which one feels better?
どっちが気持ちいいの?
This way.
こっち
This way?
こっち?
It feels better this way.
こっちの方が気持ちいいんだ
That's naughty.
やらしいね
Have you ever done a flow system?
流体制をしたことあるの?
Is it only once?
一回しかないの?
Only once.
一回しかない
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
feeling
気持ち
good?
いい?
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Ah, amazing.
あ、 すごい
I don't have a lot of back pain.
すごい腰痛くないじゃん
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
Don't you have a lot of back pain?
すごい腰痛くない?
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
Open your legs.
足開いて
Open your legs slowly.
ゆっくり足開いて
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Oh, I dropped it.
あ、落としちゃった
yes.
そう
This feels really good.
やっぱ気持ちいいこれ
It feels super good though.
超 気持ちいいんだけど
It's a strange system.
やらしい体制してる
Which system did you feel most comfortable with?
どの体制が一番気持ちよかった?
Okay.
いいよ
what?
何?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Bend your waist.
腰曲げて
What feels best?
一番気持ちいいの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気 持ちいい?
It's really tight.
すごい締まるね
I can't stand it.
我慢できないよ
It will stay like this.
このままそう
Can I put it inside?
中に出していい?
Take it out.
出して
Is it okay?
いいの?
Please take it out.
出してください
I might have a child.
子供出来ちゃうかもよ
Take it out.
出して
Is it okay if I can do it?
出来ちゃっていいの?
Dad.
パパ
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいいかな?
I'll make it here.
ここで作っちゃうよ
Will you drink it?
飲んでくれる?
Look at me.
見ててよ
Put it inside your pussy.
内から入れてごらん、おまんこに
Yes, just put it in from the inside.
そう、ぐーっと内から入れて
Can you do it here and there?
ここ、あれで出来てんの?
It went really deep.
すっごい奥まで入っちゃったね
Just touch my pussy.
ちょっと、おまんこ触ってごらん
The one that came out.
出たやつ
What are you doing now?
今、おなにしてんの?
different.
違う
different?
違う?
It kind of fell off.
なんか落ちちゃったね
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Well then, go to the shower beat.
じゃあ、シャワービート行って
Shall we go to the shower beat?
シャワービート行こうか
Shower beat.
シャワービート
Finally, have a beer.
最後、ビール吸ってさ
Look here.
こっち見て
how was it?
どうだった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
TRUE?
本当?
Wash everything, right?
全部洗うじゃね?
Yeah, wash it.
ええ、洗う
I'm here again.
また来ちゃった
Again?
またですか?
Also, it's already wasted.
また、もう無駄になってきてる
Shall I stop it once more?
もう、一回止めようか
Let's stop it, let's stop it.
止めよう、止めよう
I'm looking at you, is that okay?
見てるけどいい?
Be kind.
優しくして
gently.
優しく
Here, here
こ っち、こ
Tchi.
っち
Look here.
こ っち見て
Look at the camera.
カメラ見て
Just like that.
そのままね
It's become very important.
すごい大事になってるよ
Sorry.
ごめんね
what up?
どうした?
Hand.
手を
Because I want to see your face.
顔が見たいからさ
Shall I get on the toilet and clean it?
便器の上に乗って、洗浄をしようか
I'm taking it easy.
ゆっくりいるよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Sorry.
ごめんね
My legs are tight.
足がきつい
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
Let's do our best.
頑張ろう
My legs are tight.
足がきつい
Shall I put you on the bed?
ベッドに乗せようか
It's become very important.
すごい大事になってる
It looks like a hedgehog.
ハリネズミみたいになってる
Let's go to bed.
ベッドに行こう
Let's go to sleep.
寝ちゃおう
Let's have normal consciousness.
正常意識にしよう
You like normal consciousness the most, right?
正常意識が一番好きでしょ?
Let's do what we love the most.
一番好きなことやっちゃおう
Just a little more.
もう ちょっと
I was nervous.
神 経った
Please make it bigger.
大きくしてください
Touch my head.
頭に触って
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
気持ちいいよね?
Now that you're older, please go to sleep.
大きくなったので寝てください
I feel normal.
正常意識しちゃいますよ
slowly.
ゆっくり
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Look here.
こっち見て
look at me
俺を見て
Don't look at anyone but me.
俺以外見ちゃだめ
Look only at me.
俺だけを見て
If you're surprised.
びっくりしたらね
See you next week.
また来週